http://www.bir.org/the-federation/privacy-notice

Membership Directory
Members to be ratified (please log in)
Log in
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Membership Directory
Members to be ratified (please log in)
BIR Disclaimers
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by BIR and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, expressed or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
To the largest extent authorized by any applicable laws, we will not be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of BIR. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.
Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, BIR takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
All rights related to its content are reserved. Any use of its content is subject to prior authorisation of the rightholder.
Privacy notice
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR): BIR takes your data seriously
Your privacy is important for us and we take your data seriously.
BIR collects and processes personal data in accordance with applicable data protection legislation, in particular the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 (“GDPR”).
BIR does not collect or store any of your personal data without your consent when you are visiting this website.
BIR may however obtain your personal data in the context of interactions with you as a member, a partner, a relevant stakeholder, a supplier of goods or services or a (potential) employee.
You can find our Privacy Notice explaining why and how we collect your personal data, the measures we take to protect your data and how long we retain your data. The GDPR also grants you certain rights as a data subject.
If you have questions regarding the processing of your personal data, you can always contact us by e-mail (privacy@bir.org) or by letter to BIR, Avenue Franklin Roosevelt 24, 1050 Brussels, Belgium, Attention “Privacy”.
Stay up to date with our news, market information, legislative updates and events.
Back to top
BIR (aisbl) 24 Avenue Franklin Roosevelt 1050 Brussels Belgium
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Privacy notice
© 2020 BIR
web design by Grab it
